https://www.bibleleague.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At Bible League International (“Bible League”), we are committed to protecting your privacy and your personal information.  We believe your trust is important to the success and growth of our ministry.  We strive to use industry standard safeguards for all personal information you submit.  Please review this Privacy Policy to understand what information we collect and how we use that information.
This Privacy Policy states the privacy practices for information collected by Bible League through www.bibleleague.org (referred to as the “Site”).
Acceptance of Our Privacy Policy
By using the Site and services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any activities described in this Privacy Policy, your only remedy is to discontinue use of the Site.
Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you, and you should always exercise caution whenever disclosing information online.
Information Collected
Personal Information
Bible League collects your personal information through securely encrypted webforms when you voluntarily submit such information through the Site.  Personal information collected includes your contact information, such as name, address, email address and other information you submit through the Site.  Bible League uses such information to:
process online donations;
provide donation receipts;
fulfill requests for email subscriptions, such as e-News, Verse of the Day, Bible League International Action Report, and other information about Bible League;
resolve customer service issues;
provide you with information we think would be of particular interest; and
Site notifications, such as changes to the Site, Site maintenance, and changes to this Privacy Policy.
Financial Information
Bible League may collect financial information when you make a donation through the Site.
If you make a donation with a credit card, your credit card information is sent through an encrypted form to Bible League’s credit card processor. At no point does Bible League directly have access to your credit card information.
If you make a donation by bank transfer, your bank information is transmitted to Bible League through an encrypted web form. We will process your donation as requests and securely store your financial information.
When you make a donation, Bible League also receives your personal information.  Your personal information will be processed in accordance with this Policy.
Aggregated Tracking Information
Bible League collects several types of aggregated tracking information on the Site, mainly by tracking page views to monitor visitor traffic patterns and Site usage to help us further develop and improve the content and design of the Site. This information includes but is not limited to: IP addresses (An IP address is the unique number that is assigned to your computer automatically when you log onto the Internet.), browser types, and page views. Bible League tracks this information in order to track movement throughout the Site to analyze trends and to improve the content and features to meet your needs. We may also collect your IP address to help diagnose problems with the server and to administer the Site.
Sharing of Information with Third-Parties
Bible League is the sole owner of the information collected on the Site.  However, we may share your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information externally with third-party vendors who assist us and other parties with promoting and marketing Bible League.  These third-party vendors may also use this information to promote and market other organizations.  Promotion and marketing may include donor research, management of donor databases, promotional mailings or other targeted promotions.  Information shared may include your name, address, email address and transaction history.  You may request at any time that we do not share your name, address or other information with these third parties.
Required Disclosure of Information
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law or to comply with legal processes, such as search warrants or subpoenas. We also reserve the right to disclose your personal information if we believe the information must be shared to:
address technical problems or perform network maintenance;
protect the rights, interest or property of Bible League;
investigate reports of users sending material using a false email address, or of users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive messages;
protect against fraud, misuse or unauthorized use of our Site or ministry; or
address emergencies, such as the risk of someone’s physical safety.
Cookies
Cookies are pieces of text stored in the memory of your browser. Bible League uses cookies to track your interests and enhance your experience while visiting the Site. If you disable cookies, you can still use the Site; however, you may be limited in some areas of the Site.
Some of our third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website and other websites.  Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visits to our sites and/or other sites on the internet.  You may opt out of third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance.
Links to External Web Sites
This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through the Site. The Site contains links to external websites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy polices of these sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy policies of each website that collects personally identifiable information.
Security
The Site is designed with physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the information we collect via the Site.  Bible League takes reasonable precautions, such as encryption for all sensitive areas of the Site, including all online donations and contact forms.
However, even with such measures, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will be unable to bypass these safeguards and access the information you provide via the Site. If you have any questions about the security of our Site, please submit such questions through our Contact Us Form.
Credit Card Security
We understand the concerns you may have with using a credit card for online transactions. To relieve those concerns, we process your credit card transaction in compliance with Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards.
Opt-Out
Communications Opt-Out
If you no longer wish to receive communications, you may request removal from the contact lists by emailing your request to us at info@bibleleague.org or through the unsubscribe instructions included in all communications from Bible League.  However, because Site notifications include important information about the Site, you cannot unsubscribe to these communications.
Sharing of Information Opt-Out
You may request that your information not be shared with third-parties by completing the Information Sharing Opt-Out Form.
Updating Information
You can correct or update your personal information by completing the Contact Information Form.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. When this policy is revised, we will post the updated version to the Site. Your continued use of the Site indicates your acceptance of these changes.  This policy will indicate the date it was last updated.
Changes to this Privacy Policy were last made on February 4, 2020.
You Can Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please use our Contact Us Form or at info@bibleleague.org.
Main Menu
About Us
ERV Bibles
Contact Us
Bibles and
Downloads
Privacy Policy
What We Do
Where We Serve
Ways to Give
Donate Now
Verse of the Day
Latest News and StoriesTeen Gets Own BibleOctober 5, 2020Xhoni’s Hope in ChristOctober 5, 2020Sharing with the SickSeptember 28, 2020A Release in her SoulSeptember 28, 2020Instagram Photos
bibleleagueinternational
Samvel found hope and belonging in Christ. Read hi
Just got this picture from a partner in Zimbabwe -
Let’s choose to listen to and obey what God has
“There is almost no work here. Sometimes I clean
We are getting so many reports of Church Planter T
In the same way, you should be a light for other p
Load More...
Follow on Instagram
Subscribe
Options
eNews
Verse of the Day and Devotion
Name*
First
Last
Email*
Connect with Us
© 2020 Bible League International • 1 Bible League Plaza • Crete, IL • 60417 • 1 (866) 825-4636
Thank you for your interest in Bible League International. We are delighted to make available to you our weekly e-newsletter. Many of our friends find this very interesting and helpful. It features news from Washington, Savvy Living, gift stories, finance news and timely articles. You may receive our regular updates at no cost or obligation simply by providing your information below.
Please enable JavaScript in your browser to complete this form.Name *FirstLastEmail *Comments or QuestionsEmailSend
×
×
×
×
Get daily devotional and encouraging ministry updates in your inbox.
First
Last
*
Street Address
City
StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
×
Thank you for your gift!
You will receive a receipt by mail once your bank transfer has been completed.
If you have any questions or comments, please contact us at
info@bibleleague.org or (866) 825-4636 toll free.
We use cookies on our website to personalize your experience and improve our efforts. By continuing, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy.Ok
